<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<recommendations>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			An exceptional and enthusiastic team-player who inspires everyone around him to push the boundaries of creativity. A great addition for any company and a good friend.
		</description>
		<author>Adrian Dent</author>
		<title>Lead Project Manager, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			From all the developers that I have paired in the past, there are very few I enjoyed driving with, Ahmed being one of them. Great analytical skills, perfect problem solving approach, has debuggers wrapped around his little finger - both ActionScript and JavaScript. Always going the extra mile, he's a super team player.
		</description>
		<author>Gerhard Lazu</author>
		<title>Senior developer, ESP</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is an excellent mate, creative, proactive, fast, and with wide technological skills.
		</description>
		<author>Jesus Carrera Rodríguez</author>
		<title>Front End Developer, ESP</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is as sharp as a tack, and is a web video guru. He's helped us make a great improvement in our video offering.
		</description>
		<author>Julian Simpson</author>
		<title>Production Manager/Build and Release Manager, ESP</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is one of those people who's skills span both design and programming, he is very talented at both design and programming. He quickly orientated himself in the creative services team at Google and helped us develop a number of exciting client channel concepts for YouTube as well as creating various gadgets in Actionscript that we still use and offer to clients today. I wouldn't hesitate to recommend him to anyone, and would most definitely re-hire him in the future if needed. Ahmed is not some sort of technogeek but blended in nicely in our team and is a great help in client-facing meetings.
		</description>
		<author>Emanuel Berglund</author>
		<title>Creative Services Developer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed joined our development team initially as a 'stop gap' for a short term month placement - but he's so good we don't want to let him go! Ahmed offers a highly sought after ability which is a sometimes rare combination of a thorough understanding of commercial opportunities along with excellent front end development skills. Ahmed consistently over delivers on expectations. He is innovative and highly motivated. Ahmed is a huge asset to our organisation and our team and is a respected colleague and well liked by all.
		</description>
		<author>Sophie Neary</author>
		<title>Operations Director, ESP</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is a brilliant developer, who has a strong understanding of a large range of different technologies. He stands out from the crowd by being able to communicate all that is technical to anyone at different degrees of knowledge. Passionate and always increasing his skill and overall a great guy to work with.
		</description>
		<author>Paul Vayanos</author>
		<title>Freelance Designer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Through working on YouTube I had the bonus of working with Ahmed - I was really impressed with his knowledge, AS3 skills and his attitude both as a mentor and in tight spots and on deadline. Recommend him Creatively, Technically and Personally. 
		</description>
		<author>Tom Uglow</author>
		<title>Senior Designer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			I used to work with Ahmed on several projects, his contribution to the projects and his attitudes was always top and helped us to create the best quality outcome. He's proactive in his work and his understanding of internet based activities is a big contribution to the whole team effort. 
		</description>
		<author>Andrej Maier</author>
		<title>Senior Digital Designer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			I have worked with Ahmed on two major projects so far! Ahmed is so great to work with! He brings to the table in-depth knowledge and an eagerness to learn even more. He is also polite, friendly and a joy to collaborate with. With his skill base and incredible work ethic, it continues to be a pleasure to work with him! 
		</description>
		<author>Saina Shelton</author>
		<title>Technical Producer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			A self-starter who's keen to dive into projects and lend a hand where necessary, and who is also keen to pin-point and start new projects where there is a more long-term need. Not only does Ahmed know a great deal about his own role, but he also understands how to clearly communicate with other colleagues and clients who may not be as experienced or familiar with the topics he is discussing. He is also a very friendly, positive and creative person to work around and can be replied upon to consider and find solutions to challenges you share with him. A massive asset to the team! 
		</description>
		<author>Nicola Young</author>
		<title>Lead Account Manager (Creative Services), Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed has proved himself continuously as a talented and focussed designer. He has excellent technical knowledge and quickly established himself at Google as a go-to guy for all things Flash, Actionscript, PHP, Javascript etc. He has a great attitude and his work is concise and timely. I am very happy to recommend Ahmed; he is a great asset to any team. 
		</description>
		<author>Giles Tuck</author>
		<title>Senior Digital Designer, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is an extremely proactive designer/developer and a delight to manage. He is always learning and constantly surprises his team-mates with innovative technological solutions to a project's challenges. I would definitely like to work w/ Ahmed again in any type of project and think he's an asset to any team he joins. 
		</description>
		<author>Carlos Ferrão</author>
		<title>Project Manager, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed's solid work ethic, excellent knowledge and skill base, attention to detail and commitment to ensure the best solution to any dev project has made him an essential member to any project team. His love for his work is always evident, continuing to keep abreast of new technologies and processes, while sharing his knowledge and learnings with his team. He always asks questions, if he is unsure and quickly processes the information and applies his learning accordingly. Ahmed has excellent communication skills, owning the ability to drive a project as well as ensure all stakeholders are kept informed. He is kind, enthusiastic and a pleasure to work with. 
		</description>
		<author>Leona Farquharson</author>
		<title>Project Manager, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is quite frankly a digital prodigy! His broad digital knowledge is incredible, yet his depth of knowledge and practical experience within each of those areas is immense. His interest and passion for digital media is obvious and means that he is always keen to learn as much as he can, both in work and externally. Ahmed is a real asset to our team, he has a rare ability to communicate complex technical issues to non-technically minded staff in a way that is understandable yet not patronising. He also has a great sense of humour, positive 'can-do' attitude and willingness to do whatever is asked of him to the best of his abilities. I would have no hesitation in recommending Ahmed to other people in my position, looking to hire talented digital staff. 
		</description>
		<author>Nadine Drelaud</author>
		<title>Freelance Lead Project Manager, Google</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed is a kind, outgoing and strong person who is always willing to give advice and help others. Ahmed's web skills are immense. I believe his fantastic work ethics have contributed to his well-deserved successes to date. An asset to any company.
		</description>
		<author>Amy Forbes</author>
		<title>Graphic Designer, The Bubblegate Company Limited</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed was one of my students at Ravensbourne. During his 3 year course he developed from a driven student into a mature thinking designer without managing to loose any of his drive. His dedication to the discipline is awesome.
		</description>
		<author>John Durrant</author>
		<title>Course Leader, Ravensbourne College of Design and Communication</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed was one of my dissertation students at Ravensbourne. I found him quick to learn, very focused, intelligent and ambitious - a star in the making.
		</description>
		<author>Richard Oliver</author>
		<title>Visiting Lecturer, Ravensbourne College of Design and Communication</title>
	</recommendation>
	<recommendation>
		<description>
			Ahmed was one of the most able students I ever taught. It was always a pleasure to work with him in seminars as his ability to combine concept with technology was very inspiring. Consequently his degree project was MA/MSc level. Beyond this his interpersonal skills are excellent and he was very engaged helping in all situations. I would always offer him a place on an MA/MSc program as well as a job.
		</description>
		<author>Martin Schmitz</author>
		<title>Senior Lecturer, Ravensbourne College of Design and Communication</title>
	</recommendation>
</recommendations>
