<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<mainfeature>
	<feature>
		<title>Homepage Hero Carousel for 1Click2Fame.com</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/1c2f_carousel.jpg</image>
		<id>a1c2fCarousel</id>
		<description>
		An important aesthetic and usability feature of the new 1Click2Fame.com web site is the home page carousel. This needed to show the latest videos and allow visitors to quickly and easily vote on them. The user can flick through the different videos, load up the player in situ and if they vote no, they carousel closes the player and queues another video at random allowing for quick and simple flowing interaction.
		</description>
		<link>1click2fame.com/</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/carousel/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/carousel/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/carousel/3.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>gadget</tag>
			<tag>flash</tag>
			<tag>video</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>player</tag>
			<tag>carousel</tag>
			<tag>hero</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Flash Video Player for 1Click2Fame.com</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/1c2f_player.jpg</image>
		<id>a1c2fPlayer</id>
		<description>
		One of the main projects that I had to do at 1Click2Fame.com was to create their branded player. This is one of the most important assets of the site, for example, what would YouTube be without its player? The player needed to not only play videos but also deal with voting on a performance and also handle authentication (in situ) as well as being embedable on external site and having a JavaScript API.
		</description>
		<link>1click2fame.com/</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/player/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/player/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/player/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/player/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>gadget</tag>
			<tag>flash</tag>
			<tag>video</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>player</tag>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Hero Feature for 1Click2Fame.com Bootcamp</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/1c2f_bootcamp.jpg</image>
		<id>a1c2fBootcamp</id>
		<description>
		During my time at 1Click2Fame.com I was asked to create a flash hero feature for the Boot Camp microsite. This header will be updated at every stage during the build up to and during the Boot Camp. It also loosely integrates the new video player I'm writing for 1Click2Fame.com.
		</description>
		<link>1click2fame.com/bootcamp</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/bootcamp/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/bootcamp/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/1c2f/bootcamp/3.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>gadget</tag>
			<tag>flash</tag>
			<tag>video</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>hero</tag>
			<tag>accordion</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Tutorials for Flashtuts+</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/tuts_flash_puremvc.jpg</image>
		<id>tutsFlashPureMVC</id>
		<description>
		I've recently started writing tutorials for the web site Flashtuts+ so I can raise my profile as a skilled freelancer. I've been asked to write a few more including ones on using YouTube and Google products and APIs, and coding conventions. The first tutorial I wrote, on PureMVC, went down really well and I'll be writing about two a month now.
		</description>
		<link>flash.tutsplus.com/author/ahmed-nuaman/</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tuts/flash/puremvc/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tuts/flash/puremvc/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tuts/flash/puremvc/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tuts/flash/puremvc/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>puremvc</tag>
			<tag>tutorial</tag>
			<tag>flickr</tag>
			<tag>framework</tag>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>gdata</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
			<tag>gadget</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>	
	<feature>
		<title>Laurence Mills Channel</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/fsmg_lm.jpg</image>
		<id>fsmgLM</id>
		<description>
		My friend, Laurence Mills, required a nice and simple micro site where he could upload and publish his videos to be used as his showreel and portfolio. I suggested using a YouTube Brand Channel rather than having any old web site sitting on the web. I designed a simple style for it, running on the basis of how he created his shorts and installed the 3D Carousel Gadget that I created.
		</description>
		<link>youtube.com/laurencemills</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/lm/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/lm/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/lm/3.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>brand</tag>
			<tag>channel</tag>
			<tag>carousel</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>flash</tag>
			<tag>photoshop</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>YouTube Brand Channel 3D Carousel</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_3dcarousel.jpg</image>
		<id>ytBC3DCarousel</id>
		<description>
		During my time at Google I was asked to create some new products for YouTube. I created this new 3D carousel, much like Apple's coverflow, using Actionscript 3 with Papervision. It's been created in a way that allows it to be fully customised, from the background gradient colours to the size of the player and whether they'd like HQ/HD as standard. The gadget can be updated through changing an XML file, and a CMS for it is in production, to be built on Google AppEngine framework in Python.
		</description>
		<link>youtube.com/3dcarouseldemo</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/3dcarousel/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/3dcarousel/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/3dcarousel/3.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>brand</tag>
			<tag>channel</tag>
			<tag>carousel</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>papervision</tag>
			<tag>puremvc</tag>
			<tag>python</tag>
			<tag>appengine</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Google Advertising Landscape CMS</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/tz_galcms.jpg</image>
		<id>tzGal</id>
		<description>
			The Google Advertising Landscape (GAL for short) is an internal Google Sales tool created to aid DSOs sell Google, YouTube and GCN inventory to media buyers. It streamlines the creation of presentations, allowing sales officers to pick and customise case studies and elements to help them create the perfect pitch. I created the content management system (CMS) that the sales officers used to create their own GAL presentations. Its front-end was written in XHTML, CSS and JavaScript (jQuery) and back-end is powered by CodeIgnitor (PHP) and MySQL.
		</description>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/gal/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/gal/2.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>php</tag>
			<tag>mysql</tag>
			<tag>xhtml</tag>
			<tag>css</tag>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
			<tag>google</tag>
			<tag>jquery</tag>
			<tag>codeignitor</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>YouTube Advertising Showcase</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_adshowcase.jpg</image>
		<id>ytAdShowcase</id>
		<description>
			The YouTube Advertising Showcase is a tool that allows advertisers to see the different and innovative examples of YouTube's inventory ranging from expandable MPUs/LRECs to mastheads and brand channels. All the examples are video captured to help advertisers see the user journey. I created the front-end showcase, due to feature on YouTube, and the back-end CMS for sales officers to create and modify examples. The front and back-ends are built with Flex MXML and Actionscript 3 and uses Google App Engine (Python) for data storage and API functions.
		</description>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/adshowcase/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/adshowcase/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/adshowcase/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/adshowcase/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>mxml</tag>
			<tag>gdata</tag>
			<tag>python</tag>
			<tag>appengine</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>YouTube Brand Channel Concepts</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_bc_nissan.jpg</image>
		<id>ytBrandChannels</id>
		<description>
			As part of my work at Google, I not only had to develop internal and external applications, but I was also brought into projects as a designer. I was asked multiple times to come up with YouTube Brand Channel concepts for clients ranging from TopGear, BMW, Ford to GE. To create these brand channels, one must have an understanding of what YouTube is about (community videos), how and why YouTubers participate in competitions, and how to use the YouTube APIs.
		</description>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/brandchannels/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/brandchannels/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/brandchannels/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/brandchannels/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>brand</tag>
			<tag>channel</tag>
			<tag>carousel</tag>
			<tag>contest</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>photoshop</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>WEF Davos Debates 2009 Channel</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_bc_davos.jpg</image>
		<id>ytDavos</id>
		<description>
			The Davos Debates 2009 were a great way that YouTube helped users post their responses and feelings on major questions to the world's leaders. It featured a full custom brand channel gadget, created by me in Actionscript 2, and uses the YouTube Contest API with a Google App Engine (Python) proxy. The gadget proved to be highly successful and a first for YouTube.
		</description>
		<link>youtube.com/davos</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/davos/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/davos/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/davos/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/davos/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>brand</tag>
			<tag>channel</tag>
			<tag>contest</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
			<tag>gdata</tag>
			<tag>appengine</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>YouTube Symphony Orchestra Channel</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_symphony.jpg</image>
		<id>ytSymphony</id>
		<description>
			YouTube's Symphony Orchestra was a new and innovative projects that involved the YouTube community submitting videos of themselves and voting for their favourites to win a part in a special orchestra summit in New York's Carnegie Hall. I was brought in to help the guys with the project, on a Friday (two days before it went live), as they were having problems with the YouTube and Google GData APIs. I introduced them to the classes that I wrote for the Davos channel and helped them in integrating the player into their custom carousel and video wall.
		</description>
		<link>youtube.com/symphony</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/symphony/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/symphony/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/symphony/3.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>videowall</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>gdata</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>last.fm &amp; YouTube iGoogle Gadget Mash-up</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/yt_lastfm_mashup.jpg</image>
		<id>ytLastFm</id>
		<description>
			During my time at Google, I decided to learn as much as I could about the Google GData and YouTube APIs. I decided to do a mash-up between last.fm and YouTube, whereby it would query last.fm and return a set of artists, tracks or albums, depending on your specification, and then take this to YouTube and return the highest ranking video. It's turned out to be a great way for people to get the latest gossip and tracks from their favourite artists and has had over 50,000 visitors since October 2008.
		</description>
		<link>www.google.com/ig/adde?moduleurl=http://cs-stage5.tangozebra.com/80364/ahmed/Player.xml&amp;source=imag</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/lastfm/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/lastfm/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/lastfm/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/yt/lastfm/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>lastfm</tag>
			<tag>youtube</tag>
			<tag>gadget</tag>
			<tag>widget</tag>
			<tag>igoogle</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
			<tag>opensocial</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Coutts Location Tool</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/tz_coutts.jpg</image>
		<id>tzCoutts</id>
		<description>
			The Coutts Location Tool is a project that I created whilst working at Tangozebra, now part of Google. The client wanted an interactive and intuitive tool that allowed customers to see where Coutts branches are and how to get there. The idea was to embed Google Maps and use the Maps API to integrate fully with set locations as well as geocoding user's post codes and directions to Coutts branches.
		</description>
		<link>coutts.com/locations/index.asp</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/coutts/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/coutts/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/coutts/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/tz/coutts/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
			<tag>xhtml</tag>
			<tag>css</tag>
			<tag>jquery</tag>
			<tag>maps</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
			<tag>google</tag>
			<tag>geocoding</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Future Blogging Limited</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/fsmg_fb.jpg</image>
		<id>fsmgFb</id>
		<description>
			Future Blogging are a new copywriting company who wanted their web site to stand out from the crowd. I pitched the idea of having their web site look and feel like a magazine, as most of their work is copy. The took to the idea, loved it and have had nothing but praise about their bold image. The web site was constructed with Actionscript 2 and uses XML to bind the data.
		</description>
		<link>futureblogging.co.uk</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/fb/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/fb/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/fb/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/fb/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>photoshop</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>flash</tag>
			<tag>actionscript2</tag>
			<tag>php</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Brockway Consulting Limited</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/fsmg_bc.jpg</image>
		<id>fsmgBc</id>
		<description>
			Brockway Consulting are a company who provide consultancy for the utility, government and rail industries. They required a sleek, modern and simple web site that would give them the ability to have a blog and keep up to date. The web site delivered is CMS based and allows the company to keep their site up to date as well add new pages, it's powered by PHP and MySQL, with an Actionscript 3 main feature, and has an XHTML and CSS compliant template.
		</description>
		<link>brockwayconsulting.com</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/bc/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/bc/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/bc/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/bc/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>php</tag>
			<tag>xhtml</tag>
			<tag>css</tag>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
			<tag>jquery</tag>
			<tag>mysql</tag>
			<tag>cms</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Marshall Arts Photography</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/fsmg_mm.jpg</image>
		<id>fsmgMm</id>
		<description>
			Mandy Marshall is a photographer who I had the pleasure to work with in a previous job. She wanted a clean, modern web site but did not require the complexity of a CMS. I proposed the idea of having her upload her photos to Flickr and for my to build a web site that fed off the Flickr API and presented her photos on her own web site. The front-end is built with Actionscript 3 and MXML and uses a PHP based proxy system to interact with Flickr's API.
		</description>
		<link>marshallartsphotography.co.uk</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/mm/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/fsmg/mm/2.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>flickr</tag>
			<tag>mxml</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>api</tag>
			<tag>design</tag>
			<tag>photoshop</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>Mosaicappeals.com Web Site</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/bubb_mos.jpg</image>
		<id>bubbMos</id>
		<description>
			Mosaicappeals.com is a project that I created in a previous job. The concept was to create a self service style web site that allow charities and fund-raisers to come along and create a mosaic from any picture and have those tiles sold to the general public. The tiles sold would then count towards the charity's/fund-raiser's total. The system is built entirely on CodeIgnior (PHP) and uses XHTML, CSS, and JavaScript (Prototype and Script.aculo.us) for the front-end. The system also uses a Protx 3Dsecure API that I wrote.
		</description>
		<link>mosaicappeals.com</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/mos/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/mos/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/mos/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/mos/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>php</tag>
			<tag>xhtml</tag>
			<tag>css</tag>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
			<tag>prototype</tag>
			<tag>scriptaculous</tag>
			<tag>protx</tag>
			<tag>mysql</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
	<feature>
		<title>FosterCare UK Web Site &amp; SEO</title>
		<image>/assets/image/work/mainfeature/bubb_fcuk.jpg</image>
		<id>bubbFcuk</id>
		<description>
			FosterCare UK is a fostering agency and who I worked with in a previous job. I was in charge of creating their web site, optimising it and then creating and managing a Google Adwords PPC campaign. The web site is a CMS powered site that allows them to keep it up to date, and with the optimisation and PPC campaign, their ROI reached over 300%.
		</description>
		<link>fostercareuk.co.uk</link>
		<thumbnails>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/fcuk/1.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/fcuk/2.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/fcuk/3.jpg"/>
			<thumbnail src="/assets/image/work/screenshots/bubb/fcuk/4.jpg"/>
		</thumbnails>
		<tags>
			<tag>php</tag>
			<tag>mysql</tag>
			<tag>xhtml</tag>
			<tag>css</tag>
			<tag>javascript</tag>
			<tag>actionscript3</tag>
			<tag>seo</tag>
			<tag>adwords</tag>
		</tags>
	</feature>
</mainfeature>
